Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - #19361. Promoting medical professionalism and ethics in Vietnam, 2010 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Harvard University, 1999-2008; John F. Kennedy School of Government
      - Fulbright Economics Teaching Program at the University of Economics, Ho Chi Minh City, 2003-2005 (Box 4, Folder 28)
        John F. Kennedy School of Government
        Fulbright Economics Teaching Program
        Trường đại học kinh tế Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh
      - #9119. JFK School of Government- Fulbright economic teaching program in Vietnam, 2001-2002; Harvard University; John F. Kennedy School of Government (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - #9119. John F. Kennedy School of Government - Fulbright Economics Teaching Program, 2000-2004; Harvard University; John F. Kennedy School of Government (Box 4, Folder 30)
      - #9417. JFK School of Government. Fulbright Executive Training Program, 2001-2003 (Box 4, Folder 31)
        Fulbright Executive Training Program
      - #9417. John F. Kennedy School of Government. Progress Report to Atlantic Philanthropies. July 15, 2002, 2002-07-15 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - #9119 and #9417. Harvard/Kennedy Fulbright program. File 1, 2000-2001 (Box 4, Folder 33-34)
      - #9119 and #9417. Harvard/Kennedy Fulbright program. File 2, 1999, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - #9119 and #9417. Harvard/Kennedy Fulbright program. March 2002. File 3, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
      - #9119 and #9417. Harvard/Kennedy Fulbright program. 2002-2003. File 4, 2002-2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Trade Policy Reform and the Role of International Institutions: What Vietnam Needs to Know, Ho Chi Minh City, April 7-11, 2003, 2003-04-30; CD-5137; Fulbright Economics Teaching Program; Trường đại học kinh tế Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - #11814. John F. Kennedy School of Government - Vietnam legal education program, 2003-2005; Columbia University. School of Law (Box 5, Folder 4)
        National University of Singapore
        Columbia University. School of Law
      - #11814. Vietnam Legal Education Program. Columbia Law Program, 2001-2003; Columbia University. School of Law (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - #11814. Legal Education Program. (Harvard and Columbia), 2001-2003; Harvard University; Columbia University. School of Law (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - #11814. JFK School of Government- Vietnam legal education program, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - #13257. AIDS public policy training for Vietnam leaders, 2004-2008 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - HealthBridge Foundation of Canada, 2004-2009
      HealthBridge Foundation of Canada
      Canada
      - #13002. Building tobacco control capacity with the Vietnam Health Association, 2004, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        Hội y té̂ công cộng Việt Nam
      - #15838. Promoting the evidence base for cancer communication, 2009 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Ho Chi Minh City University of Medicine and Pharmacy, 2003-2005; Đại học Y Dược Thành phố Hồ Chí Minh
      Medical Education, Specialty Hospitals
      - #12229 Health research unit, faculty of public health, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - #12229 Health research unit, faculty of public health, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hue Central Hospital, 2003-2005; Bệnh viện Trung Ương Huế
      - #13009. Medical equipment for the Department of Pediatrics, 2003-2005 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Hue College of Medicine and Pharmacy, 2010-2011; Trường đại học y Huế
      - #19138. The 2nd International Conference Among Greater Mekong Sub-regional Countries on Challenges and Opportunities for Collaboration of Public Health Training and Research in Globalization, 2010 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        Pharmacology
      - #20489. Community-oriented transformation of health professional education and training, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Hue University, 2000-2009; Đại học Huế
      - General, 2001-2002, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Hue University/LRC (Learning Resource Center), 2000-2001, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Hue University/LRC (Learning Resource Center), 2002-2003, 2001-2004 (Box 5, Folder 18-19)
      - Hue University/LRC (Learning Resource Center), 2004, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Hue University/LRC (Learning Resource Center), 2005, 2005-2006 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Vietnam/Hue book, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - English lab, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Project proposal: Development of e-learning in medical schools submitted to the Royal Netherlands embassy in Hanoi, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 24)
        In Vietnamese and English.
      - #12739. Computer purchase for the Hue University Learning Resource Center, 2004-2005 (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - #13738. Sustainable Learning Resource Center, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - #13738. Sustainable Learning Resource Center (LRC), 2004-2008 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - #16948. Learning Resource Center ICT: infrastructure upgrade, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Institute for Global Tobacco Control, 2001-2009; Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health. Institute for Global Tobacco Control
      Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health. Institute for Global Tobacco Control
      Epidemiology
      - #13001. Reduce smoking in Vietnam campaign, 2001, 2004-2009 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The International Center/Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation, International Center; Vietnam Veterans of America Foundation
      - #15335 Establishing Community-based Mental Health resources for Da Nang City and Khanh Hoa Province, 1982, 2007-2009 (Box 235, Folder 20)
    - International Documentary Association, Northrop, Sandy, 1947-
      Northrop, Sandy, 1947-
      International Documentary Association
      - #8791. A Tale of Two Cities, 2001-2002 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - #8791. A Tale of Two Cities, 1999-2001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - #11084. Sandy Northrop. HCMC documentary (Vietnam: the Next Generation), 1999-2005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - #11084. Vietnam: the Next Generation, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - #11084. Vietnam: the Next Generation, 1999, 2002-2004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - International Network for the Availability of Scientific Publications, 2004-2009
      International Network for the Availability of Scientific Publications
      - #15691. Developing capacity for health information access and use, 2004, 2007-2009 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - John Hopkins University - Center of Communication Programs, 1992-2011; Johns Hopkins University. Center for Communication Programs
      Johns Hopkins University. Center for Communication Programs
      - #11067. Health communications in Vietnam, 1992, 2002-2006 (Box 6, Folder 11-12)
      - #11067. Health communications in Vietnam. "Enter Educate/Serial drama for TV", 2004 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - #11067. Health communications in Vietnam, 2002-2005 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - #11067. Health communications in Vietnam, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - #13879. Establishment of a Vietnam Center for Health Communication Programs, 1992, 2005-2006, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Journal Donation Project, 2010; New School (New York, N.Y.). Journal Donation Project
      New School (New York, N.Y.). Journal Donation Project
      - #19461. Core program support, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Khanh Hoa Provincial Health Department, 2003-2010; Khánh Hòa (Vietnam: Province). Provincial Health Department
      Khánh Hòa (Vietnam: Province). Provincial Health Department
      - #12223. Improving commune-level health systems, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - #12223. Improving commune-level health systems, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - #13923. Commune level facilities for primary health care in Khanh Hoa province phase II, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - #19024. Developing para-clinical laboratory facilities: a pilot intervention, 2010 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Kids First Vietnam - Greater Seattle Vietnam Association, 1998-2007; Kids First Vietnam; Greater Seattle Vietnam Association
      Kids First Vietnam
      - Kids First, 2000-2004 (Box 6, Folder 22)
        Contains photographs. Some material in Vietnamese.
      - Kids First, 2005, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Kids First, 2006, 2006 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - #5496 (#00-223). Building projects, 1998-2003 (Box 6, Folder 25)
        Rehabilitation
      - #5496 (#00-223). Building projects, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 26)
        "Formerly "Greater Seattle Vietnam Association"--original folder
      - #8789. Quang Tri Rehabilition Village, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - #8789. Quang Tri Province Rehabilitation Village 2001, 2000-2005 (Box 6, Folder 28-29)
      - #12111. People with disabilities in Vietnam study tour, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - #12111. Improving opportunities and services for people with disabilities in Vietnam. DF/JRH/ARR, 2003 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - #14152. Operational support for Kids First village in Quang Tri, Vietnam, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 32)
        Developmental Disability Services, Vocational Rehabilitation
      - #14152. Operational support for Kids First village in Quang Tri, Vietnam, 2005-2007 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Marie Stopes International, 2008-2009; Marie Stopes International (Vietnam)
      Marie Stopes International (Vietnam)
      - #16663. Building reproductive health capacity at commune level, 2008-2009 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Marie Stopes International Australia, 2005-2008; Marie Stopes International (Australia)
      Marie Stopes International (Australia)
      - #13925. Building reproductive health capacity of community health networks in Khanh Hoa Province and Danang City, 2005-2008 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Massachusetts General Hospital Palliative Care Service, 2010; Massachusetts General Hospital
      Massachusetts General Hospital
      - #19141. Integration of sustainable palliative care into Vietnam's healthcare system: a pilot project, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - MedShare International, 2011
      MedShare International
      - #20330. Improving the quality of health care systems in Vietnam through the provision of critically-needed medical supplies, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Menzies Research Institute - Menzies Centre for Population Health Research, 2002-2009; Menzies Centre for Population Health Research
      Menzies Centre for Population Health Research
      - #11527. Capacity building and transfers, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 3)
        Communicable Disease Control
      - #11527. Capacity building and transfers, 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - #13309. Non-communicable disease surveillance in Vietnam, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - #14281. Establish surveillance and monitoring system for non-communicable diseases in Vietnam, 2005-2009 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Morning Star Center, 2001-2005
      Morning Star Center
      - #10531. Center for children with disabilities in Hanoi, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - #10531. Center for children with disabilities in Hanoi, 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - #12921. Supplemental construction grant. DF/ARR, 2004-2005 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - National Center for Scientific and Technological Information (NACESTI), 2002-2010; Trung tâm khoa học tự nhiên và công nghệ quốc gia (Vietnam)
      Trung tâm khoa học tự nhiên và công nghệ quốc gia (Vietnam)
      - #12230. Translation of MARC 21 into Vietnamese, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
        Languages
      - #12230. MARC 21, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - #12230. Translation of MARC 21 into Vietnamese, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - #13737. Translation of Anglo-American Cataloguing Rules into Vietnamese. AACR2, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - #13737. Translation of Anglo-American Cataloging Rules into Vietnamese, 2005-2007, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - #14072. Vietnam library consortium development. Consortium/resources, 2005-2007 (Box 7, Folder 15)
        Some materials in Vietnamese
      - #14072. Vietnam library consortium development, 2005-2010 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Office of the National Steering Committee 33 - Ministry of Natural Resources and Environment, 2008; Vietnam. Office of the National Steering Committee 33. Ministry of Natural Resources and Environment
      Vietnam. Office of the National Steering Committee 33. Ministry of Natural Resources and Environment
      Pollution
      - #16657. International level environmental research laboratory in Vietnam, 2008 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Operation Childlife, 2011
      Operation Childlife
      - #20157. Training for child operation in Vietnam, 2011 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Pathfinder International, 2001-2009
      Pathfinder International
      - #15311. Planning grant for strengthening medical in-service training system in Vietnam, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - #15441. Establishing a continuing medical education system for Vietnam, 2001, 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - #17689. Healthcare pre-service training project for ethnic minorities, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Population Council, 2004-2009
      - #13927. Pre-interventional assessment of primary health care at commune level in three Vietnam provinces, 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - #15851. Primary health improvement initiative: dissemination of findings and micro-pilot use of evidence, 1997, 2004, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - #16660. Improving health information management capacity for primary health care in Thai Nguyen Province, 2006-2009 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Program for Appropriate Technologies in Health (PATH), 2003-2009; Program for Appropriate Technology in Health
      Pharmacies
      - #15336. Enhancing the role of pharmacies as community health care providers, 2003, 2007-2009 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Queensland University of Technology, 2001-2009
      Queensland University of Technology
      - #9132. Capacity building in public health education at Hanoi School of Public Health, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - #10140. Hanoi School of Public Health, 2000-2004 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - #10140. Curriculum development at the Hanoi School of Public Health, 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - #10140. Curriculum development and capacity building at the Hanoi School of Public Health, 2002-2007 (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - #13982. Assisting three faculties of public health in Vietnam with master planning, 2005-2006 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - #14616. Improving the capacity of public health centers in Vietnam, 2006, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - #15850. Assessing the current state of nursing profession and needs in Vietnam. DF/GL/CMC, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - #16659. Strategic development of nursing through nurse education in Vietnam, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Reach Vietnam - East Meets West Foundation, 1993-2010; Reach Vietnam; East Meets West Foundation
      Reach Vietnam
      - Financial reports January-December 2002, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - #8565. Colleges of Economics, Education, and Engineering, Danang University, 2000-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 7, Folder 35)
        Architectural plans in Vietnamese.
      - #8565. Danang University dormitory construction, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - #8565. Colleges of Economics, Education, and Engineering, Danang University, 2000-2002 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - #8567. Danang University sports center, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 38)
        Intramural Sports
        Athletics/Sports Training
      - #8567. Danang University Sports Center, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - #8567. Danang University Sports Center, 2001-2004 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - #8572. East Meets West. University Hue guesthouse, 2001, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - #8572. Accommodations, Danang and Hue Universities, 2001, 2003-2006 (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - #8572. Accommodations, Danang and Hue Universities, 2000-2001 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - #8745. Podiatric surgery project, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - #8745. Podiatric surgery project, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      - #8745. Podiatric surgery project, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - #8792. Hue University English language lab, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - #8792. English language lab/Hue University, 2001, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - #8792. English language lab/Hue Library, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - #8793. Hue/Vietnam handbook, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - #8793. Hue/Vietnam handbook, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - #8793. Hue/Vietnam handbook, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - #9144. Humantarian relief, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - #9145. Melanie Walker project, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - #9146. Core support, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - #9147. Pediatric Department, Hue Hospital, 2000-2002, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - #9148. General operating support, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - #9149. Danang General Hospital, 2001, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - #9150. Danang University information resource center, 2001-04-2001-05 (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - #9150. Danang University Information and Resource Center. (Final report only), 2004-07-15 (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - #9150. Danang University Resources and Information Center, 2001, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - #9151. Hue University Education Resource Center, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - #9152. Vietnam National University/Hanoi, 2001, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - #9153. Hue University, 2000-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - #9203. Support organization counsel/administrative fees, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - #9418. General support, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - #9431. Hue Library - stage 2 building design and construction, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - #9432. Vietnam Plus, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 25)
        VietnamPlus
      - #9646. Danang hospital emergency center, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 26)
        Emergency Rooms
      - #9646. Danang hospital emergency center, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - #9672; #10420; #10421; #9989; #9990 notification letters, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - #9672. Assessing approaches to cervical cancer in Vietnam, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - #9672. Assessing approaches to cervical cancer in Vietnam, 2001, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - #9840. Project on building a cardiovascular center for central Vietnam, 2001-2008 (Box 8, Folder 31)
        Cardiology
      - #9840. Hue heart, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - #9842. Learning Resource Center, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - #9842. Learning Resource Center. (Progress report only), 2004-07-15 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - #9989. Danang General Hospital waste water treatment and electrical systems upgrade, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 35)
        Water Pollution
      - #9990. Danang University sports center - additional funding, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 36)
        School Athletics
      - #10142. Renovation of the surgical and pediatric departments at the Quang Tri General Hospital, 2001-2004 (Box 8, Folder 37)
        Bệnh viện đa khoa tỉnh Quảng Trị
      - #10420. Humantarian projects, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 38)
      - #10421. Overhead expenses, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 39)
      - #10788. Dormitories - Thai Nguyen University's College of Medicine, 2001-2005 (Box 8, Folder 40)
        Đại học Thái Nguyên
      - #10788. Thai Nguyen University College of Medicine, 2002-2003 (Box 8, Folder 41)
      - #10788 and #13258. Dormitories - Thai Nguyen University College of Medicine, 2003, 2004 (Box 8, Folder 42)
      - #11068. Multipurpose building, Danang General Hospital, 2001-2008 (Box 8, Folder 43)
      - #11069. Hospital management capacity building, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 44)
      - #11069. Medical capacity building in central Vietnam, 2001-2005 (Box 8, Folder 45)
      - #11469. Construction and basic fitout of an English language institute at Danang University, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 46)
      - #11469. English language building, 2001-2003 (Box 8, Folder 47)
      - #11908. Overhead expenses - Atlantic projects, 2001, 2003-2005 (Box 8, Folder 48-49)
      - #11909. Humanitarian projects, 1993, 2001, 2003-2005 (Box 8, Folder 50-51)
      - #12238. Thai Nguyen University Learning Resource Center, 2001, 2003-2006 (Box 8, Folder 52-53)
      - #12238. Thai Nguyen University Learning Resource Center. Construction, 2003-2004 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      - #12605. Construction of a multi-speciality medical building at the Quang Tri Provincial Hospital, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      - #12606. Building infrastructure and providing medical equipment to the Danang Eye Hospital, 2004-2006 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      - #12749. General operating support, 2001-2006 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      - #13007. Supplemental construction grant for Danang General Hospital multipurpose building, 2004-2006, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      - #13258. Thai Nguyen University College of Medicine dorms- phase 2, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - #13261. English language initiative supplementary construction., 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 2)
        ELI Đà Nẵng
      - #13261. English Language Institute supplementary construction. Danang ELI, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - #13295. National Hospital of Pediatrics infrastructure development - phase I, 2001, 2005-2008 (Box 9, Folder 4)
        Vietnam National Children's Hospital
        Infectious and Parasitic Diseases
      - #13488. Thai Nguyen University Learning Resource Center supplementary construction, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 5-6)
      - #13489. Hue Central Hospital Cardiovascular Center supplementary construction, 2004-2008 (Box 9, Folder 7)
        Heart and Circulatory System Diseases
      - #13929. General operating support for East Meets West Foundation for 2006-08, 2001, 2005-2008 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - #13980. Phase I: campus development for the Hanoi School of Public Health, 2001, 2005-2008 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - #13980, #13981. HSPH Information Resource Center building/plan, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - #13984. Outdoor sports field for University of Danang, 2005-2007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - #14559. Medical equipment for the Cardiovascular Center at Hue Central Hospital, 2001, 2005-2007 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - #14611. Construction of a tropical disease dept and an oncology center for the Danang General Hospital, 2001, 2006-2008, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 13)
        Oncology
      - #14619. Overhead support for Atlantic projects in Vietnam in 2007-2009, 2001, 2006-2009 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - #14676. Construction and equipping the Opthamology Department and Traning Center at Hue Central Hospital, 2001, 2006-2008, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - #14817. Upgrading the capacity of Danang Eye Hospital - phase 2, 2001, 2006-2008, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - #15542. Emergency funding for post typhoon damage to Atlantic construction projects in central Vietnam. DF/CMC, 2001, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Results for Development Institute, 2009-2010
      Results for Development Institute
      - #18407. Joint learning technical workshop on universal health coverage, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - RMIT International University Vietnam - Royal Melbourne Institute of Technology Fund, 1998-2006
      - RMIT - general, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 19)
        RMIT University (Vietnam)
        RMIT University
      - RMIT - RIUV, 2000-2001; RMIT University (Vietnam); RMIT University (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - RMIT - RIUV 2001, 2000-2002; RMIT University (Vietnam); RMIT University (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
        2nd folder contains some materials in Vietnamese
      - RMIT - RIUV 2002-2003, 2002-2003; RMIT University (Vietnam); RMIT University (Box 9, Folder 23-24)
      - Freehills memoranda of advice, 2000; RMIT University (Vietnam); RMIT University (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Due diligence information, 2000-07; RMIT University (Vietnam); RMIT University (Box 9, Folder 26)